So in this video I am going to tell you
how you can close your bank account. To close your bank account
you have to
fill a form with the bank. Along with the bank loan form
you have to attach supporting documents like
your ID proof and address proof and
you have to submit it to the bank.
Some banks have the facility that you
can also send it through the post office by
post and whatever your balance is,
you can press it or withdraw cash by cheque
or in some banks it happens
that you have to visit the branch.
In this video I am going to
show you the process of
how you will download the bank loan form and
how you have to fold the form to the bank,
which supporting documents
you can attach and how you have to
submit it to the bank. So make
romantic songs on this Munishwar you are watching
my YouTube channel on technology
welcome all of you friends let's start with a
[music] kar do me
a controller form online to download
you have to open a browser in your mobile laptop
and  In the browser,
you have to search for an account close up for
money. After writing the rate form, you have to enter the
bank account you want to enter, like State Bank or
Axis Bank, then you have to
write its name here, like account
placer from SBI, then here the
website will appear in front of you in this way, if you
look at the top, it is the
official website of www.com, here
below you will find a controller liquid form, if
you click on it, the PDF will be
downloaded and you will get this point
in the rate form, here you will get an
SBI account close up form,
if you want to search another bank, like
Axis Bank or HDFC Bank,
click on HDFC Bank here, then
here you will get the Add Pepsi Bank account close up
form, you can click on it, you will see it, in
this way you will download the PDF,
you have to fold it
and by clicking you
can send it by post or if you want, you
can visit the branch and submit it along with your supporting documents,
if you have applied your Aadhar card
in the bank, then you will have to save a photocopy of the Aadhar card and
submit it, so see here  You
can, your form will be like this,
I will show you more forms here,
like if you have a bank account and
you want to download any bank, like if you want to
download ICC Bank, then search for ICC Bank,
after that if you look in the first place,
you will get the form here,
like you have to look for Axis Bank, here you have to
search for a husband of Axis Bank, here you will get a bank
manager form, this is how the
form will be, you can see the form for your saving current account, it will be
written Axis Bank,
here you will have to fill some details of your bank account,
first of all if you
look on the left side, you will find the
date here, if you look on the right side, then
account number, here you have to fill the account number, it is
also written here, you have to
enter your name, destroyed by me, yes, here
you have to take the number form and after that,
here below you will find, if you have got your ATM debit
card debited, then you will get number one,
number two, if you have got your debit card debited, then
enter its number here, you will
come down and you will find the region of pleasure account, if
you want to get this account debited, then
here  You can see the
deficiency in branch service. If you did
not like the service of the branch, then you will
tick mark it. If you find the
service of the branch too high, then you will
tick mark it. If
you have shifted to another place where there is
no Axis Bank branch, then you will tick mark it here. If you have shifted to another place where there is no Axis Bank branch, then you will tick mark it here. If
you have monthly quarter, then you
can see the balance here. If you have to maintain the
balance at this place or you are dissatisfied, then you will tick mark it. If you want to go into the bank and want to go into the private sector or
cooperative bank, then you will
tick mark it. If you
want to close the hearing with the opening bell icon, then you will
tick mark it. Whatever your
revision will be here, you will tick mark it.
After that, you will come down with it. You will get the
mobile number here. You will
fill in your mobile number here. You will
get the landline number here. You will get
DRDO on this. If you have
DD  If you have any, then tick it and you will
get it here, if you have any
Axis Bank account, if there is
any credit account in Axis Bank, then
tick mark it first, if you have
any joint
account here, then you will get its name here without
giving it, if you have to cancel it, then you will enter the
proper account number etc., then you will
enter it here below, you will get the name and
signature of all applicants, if you have a joint
account, then if your team first has a joint
account, then you will enter the name of the teams here, if it is of
two, then enter the name of two
and sign both of them,
after that it will come down here, Bank Used Only,
you do not have to fill anything here,
where Bank Used Only Bikaner, you do
not have to do anything, this entire will be
filled by the bank, you can see,
your branch name will be there,
its employee code of the branch, etc., all this is done, keep it close to your
chest, this bank's
stamp will be there and the account number etc. will be
presented by them  And only after
that your bank account
is closed and if you have any balance maintained in your background
then you
can withdraw it through Rudolph Gas or if you want then you
can also withdraw it through cheque. In this way
you can fill the Axis Bank rate form. In the
same way I will show you another
bank like ICC Bank.
If you want to click then click on ICC Bank.
Here you will find
Request to Close Up for here. You
will click and your PDF will be downloaded.
Here you will get the form.
Here you will enter the account holder's name,
saving phone number, email address,
contact number, mobile number and here the
region of close-up. Why do you
want to get the class done? Returning to India, like a
love, you are finding the chances very high
or if you want to go to the bank, then
after that you will get the
time account push below here. There will be a
controller of how much time it will take,
see here you will find where you want to take your
payment, your balance on your account.
If you have
any other ICC  If you have a bank account,
you can fill in its details here. If
you want to take it through gas, then you
can still do it. If you want to take it through cheque, then
you can not be surprised.
After that, you will find applicants here below.
You have to sign all your applicants here. This is
your first applicant, second
applicant, third applicant.
You will fill in the signatures of all your applicants here
and
you have to deposit this point in the bank here and your
account will be launched and whatever your
balance is, you can deposit it through cash or cheque.
So, in this way,
you can close your account by downloading any bank account employment form.
Or if you visit France, then this is the
form of the account or you can
also get it in the branch.
You can also submit the quantity by calling this form.
Friends,
you must have liked this small video very much. If you liked the
video, then like it to
share it with your friends. If you don't have any
problem, you can comment below and
follow us on Instagram.  You can also message me
zero nine four times for
watching see you in the next video
with Nikal Par till now leaves and take care